Guide to the Herbert L. Abrams Papers SC0858
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2007-111
  - Effects of Radiation
    - Human radiation experiments
      - Radiation effects (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Medical effects (general)
      - General (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Medicare November 2003 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Medical effects of nuclear war
      - Medical effects: correspondence and organization and statistics (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Medical effects of nuclear war (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Medical effects of survivors (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Medical problems of survivors (for Bulletin)
      - Medical problems of survivors (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Medical problems of survivors (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Survivors and nuclear war (NEIM Manuscript) 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Plague
      - Plague (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Radiation: acute
      - Radiation: acute (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Radiation: acute (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Radiation effects
      - Effects of low level-radiation (BEIR Report) (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Radiation: low-level effects (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Radiation risk (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Radiation effects (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Radiation effects (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Radiation exposure (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Radiation x-ray (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Radon (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Atmospheric effects (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Low-level radiation effects (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Radiation: low-level (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Radiation: low-level doses (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Radiation effects (general)
      - Civil defense (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Effects (general) (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Nuclear war: medical effects (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Medical treatment (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - PSR: 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Radiation: Biological effects
      - Biological effects of radiation (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Health effects of low-level radiation (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Radiation: Biological effects (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Radiation sickness
      - Radiation sickness: clinical treatment (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2014-108
  - Correspondence
    - Association of University Radiologists, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - American College of Radiology, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Board Reviews, Dr. Abrams, 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - B Miscellaneous, 1985-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - C Miscellaneous, 1984-1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Cardiac Radiology Conferences, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Carnegie Corporation, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Ronald Castellino (Chairman, Dept. of Radiology), 1973-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Cenetr Correspondence, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Chernobyl, 1987 May (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Christmas Card File Received 12/84, 1984 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Clerkship, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Clinical Medicine, 1986-1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Committee for Concerned Scientists, Inc., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Research & Technology Assessment (Neuroradiol. & Mr), 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Computer Professional for Social Responsibilty, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Continuing Medical Education, Dr. Abrams, 1985-1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Cornell, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Council on Cardiovascular Radiology, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Course: Human Values in Medicine (Medical Center), 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Course: Medical & Societal Aspects of Nuc. War...(H. Jones), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Course #237: "Modern Warfare: Nuclear, Chem., Biol., Medical & Social Aspects", 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - C.P.R., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Curriculum Vitaes - miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Micahel Curtis, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - CVIR, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Dr. Abrams' CV's, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Short Bio (for PSR), undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Biography (Nuclear), undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Brief Biographical Note, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Biography (Medical), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - D Miscellaneous, 1985-1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Decisions Magazine-Ed. Board, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Didactic Teaching Course, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Dissident Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Donations, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - E Miscellaneous, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Egan Case, 1986 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - England, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Stanford U.S./ Exchange, 1988 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - U.S. - Soviet Medical Student Exhange Program, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Faculty Senate, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Faculty Senate Meeting Agendas, Past Meetings, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - G Miscellaneous, 1986-1997 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Bellagio Appl. 9/89, 1989 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Carnegie Grant Application July, 1989, 1989 July (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Fellowship Appl. 9/89 John Simin Guggenheim, 1989 Sept. (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Guggenheim Grant Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - H Miscellaneous, 1986-1996 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Stanford/ Health & Safety Procedures, Etc., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - John Hersey, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - I Miscellaneous, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Ideal Communications, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Indian Radiolog. & Imag. Assoc, 1986 Feb. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - "Infinite Voyage", 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - International Academic Committee on Accidental Nucler War, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - International Society of Radiology, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - IOM/Council on Health Care Tech, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - IPPNW, 1985-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - J Miscellaneous, 1993-1996 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - The Robert Wood Johnson Found, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - W. Alton Jones Foundation, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - K Miscellaneous, 1985-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Henry kaplan Files: Lectires Ernst Lucas Center, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Henry S. Kaplan Memorial Lect., 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Kauffman Lecture Abrams @ BUMC 4/85, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - L Miscellaneous, 1986-1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Little Brown & Co (From Harvard), 1980-1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Abrams Angiography Third Edition, 1974-1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Little Brown Abrams Angiography - 4th Edition, 1991-1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Angiography - Little Brown & Co. (From Harvard), 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Great Books in Radiology Little Brown & Co (From Harvard), 1973-1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Yearbook Medical Publishers, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - M Miscellaneous, 1985-1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Document List (list of all docs. on discs), 1990 Dec. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Malpractice, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - McCormick Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - No Buyline, 1989 March (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Medical Decision making, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Medicine and global Survival, 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - The Ruth Mott Fund, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - MRI, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Murray, Dr. Joseph E., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - N Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - NASCR - Scientific Program, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - National Academics of Practice, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - National Center for Radiation Risk Assessment, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - New Oxford Medical Companion, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - New Prospect Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Northeast Asia Health Comparison Study (Center), 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - NIH, 1985-1989 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - W.W. Norton "The Pres. has been shot", 1992 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - W.W. Norton & Company, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - IPPNW & The Nobel Prize, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - 1985 Nobel Peace Prize Award (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - North Anerican Society for Cardiac Radiology, 1974-1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - North American Soc. for Cardiac Radiol. Training Grants in Cardiovas. Radiology, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - North American Soceity for Cardiovascular Radiologists, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Nuclear Materials - Misc., undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - O Miscellaneous, 1985-1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - P Mscellaneous, 1985-1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Physicians for a National Health Program, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Proofreaders' Marks, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Physicians for Human Rights, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Physicians for a National health Program, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - PSR-Correspondence, 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - PSR - General Information, 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - PSR Long Range Planning, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - PSR - Presidential Selection Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - PSR - Annual Meetings, 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - PSR Travel Reimbursement Forms, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Post-Graduate Education, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - PSG Publishing; PGR, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - PSR Quarterly/ Ed. Board, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Press Articles on Dr. Abrams, 1986-1990 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Stanford Observer Article Dr. Abrams, 1985 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Press Clippings (From Harvard), 1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Q Miscellaneous, 1987 Jan. 5 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Letter from Robins to Abrams: "Hero and Antihero in History", 1997 Aug. 7 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Letter from Robines to Converse: " Polticial Paronoia: The Psychopolitics of Hatred", 1986 Nov.-Dec. (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Letter from Rudenstine to Harvard Medical School Community, 1996 May 29 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Slide Radiology in Trauma of the Liver, Spleen, & Kidneys, 1985-1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Radiologic Society of N. Ameri. (RSNA), 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Radiation Carcinogensis, 1984 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Radiology Research & Education Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Religious Holidays - Stanford, 1986 Sept. 12 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Research Assistanships - Applications, 1986 Jan. 15 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Research Assistant Info. (Hiring), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Rating the Residents, 1986-1990 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Renal Angiography in the Era of Cross Sectional Imaging, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Resident Conferences: Handouts, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Resident Information (Radiology), 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Reprints Records of Reprints Sent Out, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - David Rogers, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Rosters, 1986 Oct. 30 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - The Royal College of Radiologists, 1985-1991 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Royal College of Surgeons in Ireland, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Gold Medal Award of RSNA, 1985 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - S Miscellaneous, 1985-1996 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Scientific Aspects of Global Security, 1985-1991 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Selma Shapiro Inc., 1992 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Slides - Billing (outside), 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Society of Cardivascular and Interventional Radiology, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Society for Medical Decision Making, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Society of Thoracic Imaging, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Soviet Union: Addresses, 1988 May (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Stanford Statistics, 1969-1985 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - STS Program Content Committee, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Susan Stern - Funds See also Gift Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Susan Stern Projects, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - T Miscellaneous, 1986-1996 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Tax Exemption Letter - Stanford, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Teaching Film Files, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous Typing for Dr. Abrams, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - U Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - University Committees, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - ASSN of University Radiologists, 1985-1994 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Publications and Manuscripts
    - Stanford University School of Medicine: Department of Diagnostic Radiology and Nuclear Medicine, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Prmiary documents, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Primary documents, 1973-1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Academic Fraud, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Primary Documents, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - PGR Files, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - CT Evaluation of Renal Infection, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - CT Evaluation of Renal Infection, 1997 Feb. 27 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Problem Children: Common Fractures Commonly Missed, 1997 Jun. 30 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Test Key, Problem Children: Common Fractures Commonly Missed, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - CT, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Bob Dole M5, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Clinical Imaging of Abnormal Hernias, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Wakeforest Law Review Volume 30 Number 3, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Research in Diagnostic Radiology: A Holistic Perspective, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Can the Nation Afford a Senior Citizen As President? The Age Factor in the 1996 Election and Beyond, 1997 Apr. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - The Age Factor, 1997 Feb. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Ethical Issues in Technology Assessment, 1988 Feb. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Human Reliability and Safety in the Handling of Nuclear Weapons, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - The Vulnerable President & The 25th Amendment, 1995 Jun. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Cardiac Radiology Histroy, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Other News Articles & Reviews, 1989-1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Decisions in Imaging Economics, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - List of Files & Letters of Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - The Earth Pledge, 1993 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - The Pharos, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Publisher's Weekly, 1992 Jan. 6 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - The Earth Pledge, 1993 Dec. 17 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Office Info., 1996 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Radiology, 1992 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - San Francisco Chronicle Review, 1992 Feb-Mar. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - The Stanford Daily, 1992 Dec. 9 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Vincent Caroll Interview, Rocky Mountain News, 1992 Apr. 19 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Vineyard Gazette, 1992 Aug. 21 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - News Articles, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Academic Medicine, 1993 May (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - American Journal of Roentgenology, 1992 Nov. (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Boston Globe Review, 1992 Feb. 4 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Campus Report, 1995 Feb. 15 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Investigative Radiology, 1992 Nov. (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Kirkus Review, 1991 Dec. 1 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Library Journal, 1991 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Los Angeles Times Reviews, 1992 May 27-31 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Louisville Courier Review, 1993 Mar. 4 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - National Review, 1992 Apr. 13 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - New Englang Journal: Review, 1992 Aug. 6 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - New York TImes Review, 1992 Mar. 10 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - The New York Times Op-Ed, 1995 Jan. 4 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - The New York Times Op-Ed, 1992 Dec. 3 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - The New York Times National Sunday, 1993 Jan. 17 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Palo Alto Weekly, 1992 Apr. 1 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Oversight Committee for CME Stanford, 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - The Journal of American History, 1993 Mar-Apr (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Radiology Modern Warfare, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Activities, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - The President's Health & THe Public's Right to Know, 1994 May (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - RSNA Gold Medal - Letters to Dr. Abrams, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - 97th American Roentgen Ray Society Annual Meeting, 1997 May 4-9 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Society of Thoracic Radiology, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Society for Health Services Research in Radiology, 1997 Sept. 17-19 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Presidential Health and The Public Interest: The Campaign of 1992 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Lectures 1996 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Physicians for a National Health Program, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Radiological Society of North America, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Chernobyl: The Emerging Story; Bull. Atomic Sc., Aug/Sep 1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript - "Is the Nation Prepared for 'Caualties at a Higher Rate' Than Any Other War in History?", 1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Article in Le Monde, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Don't Link U.S.-Soviet Exchanges to Human Rights: Scientist, 1988 Jun. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Linkage, Bridges and the Human Right to Survival (The Scientist), Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Medical Supply and Demand in the Post-Nuclear War World -- copies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Obstacles to Meaningful Primary Data Gathering, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Medical Supply and Demand in the Post-Nuclear War World -- original, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - MRI: Consensus Conference JAMA, 32241 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Chapter on the Nobel Prize by J. Stoia & H. Abrams, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Nuclear Radiation in Warfare: The Physician's Role (UMEA), Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - UMEA Sweden, Nov. 10-11, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Page Proofs from UMEA, 1989 May. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Pugwash Manuscripts, 1989 Jul. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Reflections on a Lecture Tour of the U.S.S.R., Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Comments on IPPNW Trip to the Soviet Union, Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Resolved: That Nuclear Weapons Should be Abolished by Year 2000, Undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Risky Business: Fall., Disabil. & Nuclear Weapons - Harvard Bull., Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - The Shadow of Accidental Nuclear War - Conference on Evil, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - The Social Responsibility of Radiologists/ Diag. Imaging, Undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Sources of Human Instability in the Handling of Nuclear Weapons - copies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Sources of Human Instability in the Handling of Nuclear Weapons - original, Undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Strategic Defense & Inad. Nuc. War - Copenhagen (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Summary and Perspective: With Some Observations on Informed Consent -- copies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Symposium on the Medical Implications of Nuclear War - Medicine & War, Undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Unacceptable Risk: Accidental or Inadvertant Nuclear War - Lancet, Undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Unacceptable Risk: SDI & Inadv. Nuclear War - Copenhagen, 1990 Jul. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - "When the President Becomes Ill: The Role of the 25th Amendment", PSR Quarterly, 1991 Dec. (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Who's Minding the Missiles?, The Sciences, July/Aug 1986 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Who's Taking Care of Our Nuclear Weapons? - Original, 31358 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Who's Taking Care of Our Nuclear Weapons? - Original - short version, Undated (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Why Get Excited About Dan Quayle - sub. to the NYT, 1988 Oct. (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - "The Worst Effects w/ Emmerge SL" - New York Times, 31536 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Informed Consent, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Manuscript - Informed Consent, Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Manuscript: The Illusion of Longterm Survival, Undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Manuscript: International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Medical Problems of Survivors of Nuclear War., N.E. J. of Med., 1981 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Manuscript: In the Aftermath: A Doctor's View of Nuclear War, Undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Nuclear War - In the Aftermath, Undated (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Manuscript - Medical Problems of Survivors of Nuclear War Med. Resources: Availability vs. Need, Undated (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Medical Resources After Nuclear War, JAMA - Vol. 252, No.5, 30897 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Prescription for Survival: The Doctor's Dilemma. Investigative Radiology, Undated (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Manuscript - Prescription for Survival - Abrams, Undated (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Grant Application, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Consensus Conference Comments Re: MRI Update, Feb. 1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Consensus Dev. Conf. on MRI - Correspondence/Incl. Program, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Consensus Dev. Conf. on MRI - Notes on Conference, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Consensus Dev. Conf. on MRI - Final Report + Talk by HLA, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Consensus Dev. Conf. on MRI - Press Articles on Conf., Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Articles on MRI for Consensus Conference, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Articles on MRI for Consensus Conference, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Radiologic Guide, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Radiologic Guide, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Adrenal Study, Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Adrenal Study, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Manuscript - Adrenal Abnormalities Recognized on CT Scans of Patients w/ Malignant Diseases, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript - Work-Up of Adrenal Disease - Hussain & Swerdlow, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript - The Angiographer-Interventionalist and the Litigious Patient, Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Dissection of Aorta, Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Significance of Asymptomatic Renal Disease, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Resident Seminar, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Manuscript - The 1982 Caldwell Lecture - The Collateral Circ: Response to Ischemia (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Harrison Chapter Photographs, Undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Manuscript - Computed Tomography of the Kidney, Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - VA Hospital - Palo Alto (VA Service-Sharing Agreement), Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - VTSS, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - The Western Journal of Medicine, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Adam Wolfberg, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Who's Who, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Abrams' Angiography, Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Arteriography, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Copyright Permissions for Manuscripts, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Manuscript Awards, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - HLA Figure for IOM Book, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Accidental or Anadv. Nuclear War - Figure (extra copies), Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Nuclear Outlines - work in progress (HLA), Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Nuclear Manuscripts - in progress, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Desert Storm? Or Thyroid Storm?, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Accidental or Inadvertent Nuclear War. Preventive Med., 31698 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Assassination Attempt on Ronald Reagan - Chapter 11 of Book Manuscript "The Next Time", Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Assassination Attempt on Ronald Reagan - Conf., Disability & 25th Amendment (Version for Stanford Magazine), Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Assessing Diagnostic Technology: Problems & Challenges - Decisions Magazine, Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - "Booze, Drugs & Nuclear Weapons" - San Francisco Chronicle, 31669 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Caution! Presidency May be Hazardous to Your Health - NY Times Op Ed, 33724 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Dealing w/ Presidential Disability: Assassination Attempt on Reagan, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)